[{"answer": "It's my friend. Tell me you love me", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I've got a confirmed place and time", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Where ya going", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Please. Nobody goes there for the hot wings. You got a tip", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hooters. I go there for the hot wings", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You got a hundred bucks on you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You know what? We need to talk about our relationship", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, but you made out with me", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Not now, my friend", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Hey, I owe everybody money", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "We didn't break up over a stupid article. We broke up because she is a cheating, manipulative liar", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Why wouldn't I be able to handle this", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend's busy shopping.  He thinks he can handle Xmas", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah? I want a bonus for getting through the holidays without stabbing anyone with a fork", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We used to be together. Back when I was young and foolish", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And I was slumming", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And I was confused", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And I was drunk", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I would have figured it out on my own, trust me", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You think about that much? Me being the last man alive? Am I naked in this fantasy", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " This is like the third card they've given me..", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Don't tell me to take it easy, now we have to go all the way downstairs again..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " What was what", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How could I find anything? I'm not the detective", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "A platonic relationship. Working together", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Trusting each other", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Um..", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Yes. Yes I am", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I was possibly out of line..", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Ok, ok, I was wrong", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No. I'm fucking with you. For fun. Just for my own personal enjoyment..", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "O", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Now lets find something to cut these ropes off..", "docId": "Bounty-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Trust m", "qsentId": 34}]